ADRIAN WZOREK

Front-end developer | IT

CONTACT

- 784-616-234
- **■** awzorek23@wp.pl
- Q Lidzbark Warmiński
- /adrian-wzorek

EDUCATION

University

2021 - present University of Warmia and Mazury

CERTIFICATIONS & COURSES

- Driving licenses
- Karate educator cours
- Summer camp counselor

SKILLS

- Computer literate
- Communication skills
- Problem-solving skills
- Organization and time management skills
- Collaboration skills
- Adaptability
- English B2

PROFILE

I am an ambitious final-year student at the University of Warmia and Mazury in Olsztyn with a passion for sports. With over 5 years of experience participating in various tournaments and collaborating in numerous training camps, I have developed key skills such as self-motivation, composure, and adaptability in challenging situations. Since beginning my journey in IT, I have been dedicated to enhancing my skill set through several personal, non-commercial projects. Additionally, my extensive work with computers has expanded my knowledge and proficiency in the Microsoft Office suite.

WORK EXPERIENCE

CAMP EDUCATOR AND SPORTS TRAINER

UKS "Zdrowie" Lidzbark Warmiński

2018 - present

- Managed groups.
- Prepared specific types of training tailored to individual predispositions.
- Collaborated with other educators.
- Organized and performed specific events.
- Adapted to unexpected situations.

FRONT-END DEVELOPER

University project with company - GlobTree

February 2024 - June 2024

- Wrote project documentation.
- Prepared forms with specific conditions.
- Worked using the Kanban methodology.
- Managed a gifted database and integrated it with the front-end.
- Collaborated with others